Danila Doroshenko

Contact

+380964647000

ddddanchik@gmail.com

Additional Skills

- Experience in Python development
 - Parsing with BS
 - Web scraping with selenium
 - HTTP requests
- SQLite and PostgreSQL database management

- Teamwork & collaboration
- API design knowledge
- Experience building clientserver architecture
- Research models using Tensorflow, Sklearn, Keras

• Front-end: HTML/CSS/JS,

¡Query, Bootstrap

· Back-end: Django

Professional Summary

Software Engineer who is familiar with helping to create detailed application codes and design. Extensive collaboration with developers to draft and test programs for in-field rollout. Experience with Python and Git development environments to standardize and customize CI/CD. The ability for generating automation frameworks and procedures like parsing, web scraping, and HTTP requests.

Work Experience

03/2020 - Current

Make it in Ukraine
• Developed an asynchronous telegram chatbot

(@MakeItInUkrainebot) for IT talents using parsing with Beautiful Soup, telegram API, aiogram and SQLite database which led to automatization of Vacancies and Articles notifications depending on each user subscription and interests, that stores in the database.

• Implemented the quick apply feature by saving user's data into the database, shortening generated mailto link by web scrape my link shortener (a pet project that shortens links using NodeJS, MongoDB and Express) and attaching the link to every vacancy which led to better UX and makes the application process available in one click.

10/2019 - 03/2020

Rothem

Researched a computer vision real-time semantic segmentation model in deeplab (mobilenetv2) trained on Cityscape dataset, quantized it for coralTPU, and transformed it to TFlite to run in AWS via SSH connection to Raspberry pi 3.

Education

09/2020 - 11/2020

KNU, CSC

A freshman pursuing a Bachelor's degree in Software engineering and intelligent software systems.

01/2013 - 06/2020

Lyceum 142

Technical high school diploma

Certificates and articles

- Google Code-in 2019 competition
- FCE B2 English level
- Tutorial on Polynomial regression: https://colab.research.google.co m/drive/1-sY2pAgx1rYEuRXn6Tr ojfXq7PDGotR